

Accomplished Senior Software Developer with 10 years of experience leading projects by acting as architect, developer, and programmer analyst. Proficient in supporting project deliverable and maintaining releases. Strong leader in guiding support teams and solving complex issues. Steadfast in planning and implementing effective development strategies based on industry best practices. I have 3 Years as Technical Leader Project Management and Execution experience.

Rajesh Gondalia

Technical Leader

Contact

Address

Surat, India 395010

Phone

+919723657967

E-mail

rajeshgondalia 1 402@gmail.c om

Skills

Asp.Net MVC 3/4/5, Asp.Net C#, Web Service

Excellent

Asp.Net Core 2.2/3.1/5/6/7, Asp.Net Core Web API

Excellent

Entity Framework Core, LINQ

Very Good

HTML, Java Script, CSS, Jquery, Bootstrap

Work History

2023-12-16 Current

Technical Leader

Protominds Software Solution Pvt Ltd - Chennai

I am working as Technical Leader position with full time development with US based **Johnson Control** Client. They have CRM product. I am working as full stack development.

- I am working in CRM product using below technology.
- Asp.Net Core 7, Entity Framework Core, LINQ, MVC
 Architecture with Repository services, NUnit, SQL Server
 2022
- Angular 17 with Typescript, Karma Unit Test
- Azure CICD Pipeline, Github, DevOps

2023-03 2023-10

Technical Leader

HCIActive India, Ahmedabad

- I worked with Technical Leader position In Health care domain as back end developer and help to ir developers.
- I worked with agile methodology and as part of developer attend the daily scrum call.
- I worked on below technology in US health care products and it's business concept same as LIC
- Asp.Net Core 5, WPF, WCF, JQuery, MVC
 Architecture with Repository service, SQL Server
 2020

2021-11 *-* 2023-01

Senior Software Developer

HealthTech India, Ahmedabad

 Monitored ongoing operation of assigned programs and responded to problems by diagnosing and correcting logic and coding Good

Angular 10, Angular 17

Good

Microsoft SQL Server 2008.2012.2019.2022

Very Good

MySQL, PostgreSQL

Good

errors.

- Developed databases, programs and processes for integration and implementation across enterprise.
- Updated old code bases to modern development standards, improving functionality using below technology
- Asp.Net Core 5, Web API, Angular 10, SQL Server 2019, SVN

2019-10 -2021-09

Technical Lead

Narola Infotech, Surat

- Investigated system issues and implemented resolutions to reduce downtime.
- Improved systems with addition of new features and infrastructure.
- Assessed project milestones and team performance to keep staff on-task.
- Organized system operating procedures to strengthen controls.
- I have structure level expertise in below technology
 - Asp.Net With C#, Asp.Net With MVC4&5
 - Asp.Net Core 2.2&3.1, SQL Server 2019
 - Jauery Ajax, Web API

Senior Software Developer

Gyrus Systems, Surat

- Monitored ongoing operation of assigned programs and responded to problems by diagnosing and correcting logic and coding errors.
- Developed databases, programs and processes for integration and implementation across enterprise.
- Trained new developers and programmers on company standards for design and review.
- Updated old code bases to modern development standards, improving functionality.
- Project Name: Learning Management System Technology:
 - Asp.Net Core 2.2 Web API
 - Entity Framework
 - LINQ
 - SQL Server

2019-02 -2019-09

- Angular JS

2017-07 -2019-01

Software Developer

ASK-EHS Engineering & Consultants PVT LTD, Surat

- Updated old code bases to modern development standards, improving functionality.
- Collaborated with project managers to select ambitious, but realistic coding milestones on prerelease software project development.
- Designed intuitive graphical user interfaces to improve user experience.
- Collaborated on stages of systems development lifecycle from requirement gathering to production releases.

2014-11 -2017-06

Sr. Software Developer

ELaunch Solution Pvt. Ltd., Surat

- Trained new developers and programmers on company standards for design and review.
- Developed databases, programs and processes for integration and implementation across enterprise.
- Monitored ongoing operation of assigned programs and responded to problems by diagnosing and correcting logic and coding errors.
- Collaborated with project managers to select ambitious, but realistic coding milestones on prerelease software project development.

2014-07 -2014-10

Software Developer

Psk Technology, Surat

I worked on Health Care Related Project and used below technologies.

- Asp.Net MVC and Web API
- Jquery
- SQL Server 2012

Education

2011-01 -2014-08 Master of Computer Applications: Computer Software And Media Applications

SRIMCA - Bardoli, Gujarat

Accomplishments

• PROJECT - 1

Project Name: ShopRx.net

Duration: 1 Year

Team Member: 3 Team Member and I am Tech

Lead

Used Technology:

Front-End: Asp.net.Net Core 2.2 Razor With Ling,

Ajax

Back-End: SQL Server Management Studio 2019
Description: There are three modules and mail purpose of the project is admin will manage pharmacy and distributors. Distributors are upload your own medicine and pharmacy will purchase all the medicine. 1] Admin 2] Pharmacy 3] Distributor

• PROJECT - 2

Project Name: Copalana.org

Duration: 1 Year

Team Member: 3 Team Member and I am Tech

Lead

Used Technology:

Front-End: Asp.net MVC Razor With Entity

Framework, Ajax, Jauery

Back-End: SQL Server Management Studio 2014 Following more projects are completed with satisfied to client.

Description: There are four modules and mail purpose of the project is admin will manage VM, HCL and CF. This is Crowd Funding platform. 1]

Admin 2] VM 3] HCL 4] CF

PROJECT - 3

There are 3 L&T projects are successfully completed.

Project Name: [A] L&T JTBC [B] Digital Report Book

[C] L&T Raws Portal Duration: 6 Months

Team Member: 2 Team Member (Development as

well as Team Lead)

Used Technology: Front-End: Asp.net MVC 4 Razor

With Entity Framework, Ajax, Jquery

Back-End: SQL Server Management Studio 2014

Description : There are three project had completed

to L&T Defence.

Following more projects are completed with satisfied to client.

- · Password Generator (Asp.Net With C#)
- · Drag and Drop File Upload Features and Uploaded Image store in Azure (Asp.Net MVC 4)
- Progressive Web Application existing project work (Asp.Net MVC 4)
- ·LMS application (Angular 7)
- · Pharmacy domain project (Asp.Net Core 2.2 with Jquery)
- · NopCommerce (Asp.Net Core 3.1 & JQuery)

PROJECT - 4

Project Name: LMS

Product Duration: 7 Months
Team Member: 15 Members

Used Technology:

Front-End: Asp.net MVC4 Razor With AngularJS,

Entity Framework , Ajax

Back-End: SQL Server Management Studio 2012 Description: LMS Module 1] IDP 2] Employee 2]

Organization 3] Job 5] Configuration 6]

• PROJECT - 5

Project Name: SafeBajaj, SafeSubMVC, SafeZydus

Duration: 1 Year and 3 Months

Team Member: 4
Used Technology:

Front-End: Asp.net MVC3 Razor With AngularJS,

Entity Framework, Ling, Jquery and Ajax

Back-End: SQL Server Management Studio 2010

Description: Safety Projects 1] User and Role

Management Module 2] Audit Module 2] Inspection

Module 3] CAPA Module 5] Configure Email

Templates 6] Reports

• PROJECT - 6

Project Name: Appolo Tyres

Duration: 3 Month Team Member: 6 Used Technology:

Front-End: Asp.net MVC3 Razor With AngularJS,

Entity Framework, Ling, Jquery and Ajax

Back-End: SQL Server Management Studio 2010

Description: Construction Projects 1] User and Role

Management Module 2] Worker and Vehicle

Registration Module 3] Inspection Module 4] Worker

and Vehicle Identity Pass Print With Barcode 5]

Configure Email Templates

• PROJECT - 7

Project Name: Mobigo Duration: 2 Month

Team Member: 2 Used Technology:

Front-End: Asp.net C# with Three Tier Archtecture (.NET Framework 4.0) Java script Jquery with Ajax Back-End: SQL Server Management Studio 2008 R2 Description: 1] Online Shopping Website 2] Online shopping using payUmoney and also cash back money at that time provide different cash back offer. 3] Online mobile recharge and dish to recharge 4] Different category wise every product display and online shopping facility

• PROJECT - 8

Project Name: Apanaghar

Duration: 2 Month Team Member: 1

Used Technology:

Front-End: Asp.net C# with Three Tier Architecture (.NET Framework 4.0) Java script JQuery with Ajax Back-End: SQL Server Management Studio 2008 R2

Description: Binary Plan MLM

• PROJECT - 9

Project Name: DFoodBuddy

Duration: 6 Month Team Member: 2 Used Technology:

Front-End: Asp.net MVC5 with Razor, Entity

Framework 5, Linq Jquery and Ajax

Back-End: SQL Server Management Studio 2015 R2 Description: 1] This site had been look like a food panda. 2] Online restaurant and restaurant wise table booking and online food order using paypal payment gateway 3] This site had been admin as well as vendor panel managed.

• PROJECT - 10

Project Name: Apanashop

Duration: 4 Month Team Member: 1 Used Technology:

Front-End: Asp.net MVC5 with Razor, Entity

Framework 5, Ling Jauery and Ajax

Back-End: SQL Server Management Studio 2015 R2 Description: 1] This site had been completed online shopping site such as online product purchase and show category wise product display in home page.
2] Order product using payumoney payment
gateway 3] Mobile recharge and DTH recharge.

Certifications

2020-04	Microsoft Certified Asp.Net MVC Development 70- 486 Passed out 2020
2021-11	Professional Scrum Master 1 Passed out 2021
2022-10	AZ-900 Passed out 2022